<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ruolan0806.github.io</id>
    <title>HHC Food</title>
    <updated>2020-06-14T19:11:51.445Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ruolan0806.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ruolan0806.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>HHC Food</subtitle>
    <logo>https://ruolan0806.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://ruolan0806.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2020, HHC Food</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home]]></title>
        <id>https://ruolan0806.github.io/post/home/</id>
        <link href="https://ruolan0806.github.io/post/home/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-06-14T07:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://ruolan0806.github.io/post-images/1592161894664.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Product]]></title>
        <id>https://ruolan0806.github.io/post/product/</id>
        <link href="https://ruolan0806.github.io/post/product/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-06-14T01:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our products in the United States contains 25% of eel sauce (including soybeans sauce) in each individual package, it's packed with different amount of sauce according to different regions’preference. For example, customers in Japan and South Korea have different preferences for the amount of eel sauce that is packed. We will customize the percentage of sauce according to our client's preferences.<br>
We implement the business policy of maintaining high quality with reasonable price, we put customer first, and we are seeking sustainable development, we are looking forward to do business with you.<br>
HHC Food Company</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></title>
        <id>https://ruolan0806.github.io/post/manufacturing/</id>
        <link href="https://ruolan0806.github.io/post/manufacturing/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-06-14T01:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Fuqing Qixiang Food Co., Ltd., a Sino-foreign joint venture established in 1993 with a total of more than 200 employees, a manufacture that covers an area of 20,000 square meters in Fujian, China. Over the past 29 years, Our company has introduced two production lines of charbroiled eel (Unagi), with an annual output of more than 5,000 tons of Unagi, Since its establishment, we have devoted ourselves to the production and operation of fine Unagi.</p>
<p>With our excellent quality, our Unagi has become one of the best-selling products in overseas, Our products are mainly exported to United States, Japan, Russia, South Korea, Australia and as well as other countries and regions, we had reached a strategic partnerships with many well-known Japanese companies.</p>
<p>Our company registered with the FDA and granted the ISO9001-2015 Quality Management System Certification, the QS Certification as well as the HACCP System Certification. Our top quality Unagi is among the best in the industry and has been recognized and praised by customers.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Office]]></title>
        <id>https://ruolan0806.github.io/post/hhc-company-description/</id>
        <link href="https://ruolan0806.github.io/post/hhc-company-description/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-06-12T12:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our Direct Sale Office in United States is under business name of Jinling International Trading Company that locates in Coral Springs, FL.  For over 2 years of operation in south Florida, we have gained dozens of food suppliers in South Florida as our customers who have been continuing ordered our Unagi. We are working on to launch sale offices in Central Florida, Northwest Florida and later on in Georgia as well as other states.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contact us]]></title>
        <id>https://ruolan0806.github.io/post/contact-us/</id>
        <link href="https://ruolan0806.github.io/post/contact-us/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-06-10T23:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="contact-us">Contact us ！🤝</h1>
<h2 id="hhc-international-trading-company">HHC International trading company</h2>
<h2 id="tel-9176699550">Tel: 9176699550</h2>
<h2 id="email-jason1202016gmailcom">Email: jason1202016@gmail.com</h2>
<h2 id="sales-email">Sales email:</h2>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>